Fury the Merciless: We are here to meet the Legendary Orc who has been reborn!
Fury the Merciless: Warriors, face forward! Our future leader is coming!
Fury the Merciless: Our wise shaman realized that these aliens are part of the prophecy!
Fury the Merciless: With her magic, this redhead... I mean the mighty Eladia...
Fury the Merciless: will open the portal and reach the one we've been waiting for!
Fury the Merciless: He will come to us, and a new era will begin!
Fury the Merciless: Begin!
Fury the Merciless: Look! He is here! He has arrived!
Landfill Warrior: Glory to the new Horde!
Landfill Warrior: The world will fall at our feet! The Orcs will rule the world!